[
	{
		"language": "it",
		"front": "so, in any case",
		"back": "quindi, in ogni caso;pr=OHN-yee-KAH-zoh",
		"whenCreated": "2024-12-17 18:32:06",
		"extras": "pr=OHN-yee-KAH-zoh"
	},
	{
		"language": "it",
		"front": "so for example",
		"back": "quindi, ad esempio;pr=ay-ZEM-pee-oh (not SEM)",
		"whenCreated": "2024-12-01 00:00:00",
		"extras": "pr=ay-ZEM-pee-oh (not SEM)"
	},
	{
		"language": "it",
		"front": "but it's also very easy",
		"back": "ma Ã¨ anche molto facile;pr=FAH-chee-lay",
		"whenCreated": "2024-12-17 18:27:32",
		"extras": "pr=FAH-chee-lay"
	},
	{
		"language": "it",
		"front": "Therefore",
		"back": "quindi;pr=QUEEN-dee",
		"whenCreated": "2024-12-17 17:47:04",
		"extras": "pr=QUEEN-dee"
	},
	{
		"language": "it",
		"front": "of fundamental networking concepts",
		"back": "dei concetti fondamentali di rete; pr=day-kon-CHET-tee; pr=RAY-teh",
		"whenCreated": "2024-12-17 17:43:36",
		"extras": "pr=day-kon-CHET-tee; pr=RAY-teh"
	},
	{
		"language": "it",
		"front": "and finally",
		"back": "e infine; pr=in-FEE-nah",
		"whenCreated": "2024-12-17 17:42:03",
		"extras": "pr=in-FEE-nah"
	},
	{
		"language": "it",
		"front": "that you knew",
		"back": "che tu conoscessi; pr=kon-oh-SHEH-see",
		"whenCreated": "2024-12-17 17:37:47",
		"extras": "pr=kon-oh-SHEH-see"
	},
	{
		"language": "it",
		"front": "and at the end of the course",
		"back": "e alla fine del corso; pr=KOR'-soh (not zoh)",
		"whenCreated": "2024-12-17 17:28:03",
		"extras": "pr=KOR'-soh (not zoh)"
	},
	{
		"language": "it",
		"front": "in recent years",
		"back": "negli ultimi anni",
		"whenCreated": "2024-12-17 17:23:50",
		"extras": ""
	},
	{
		"language": "it",
		"front": "for React developers",
		"back": "per gli sviluppatori di React",
		"whenCreated": "2024-12-17 17:25:27",
		"extras": ""
	},
	{
		"language": "it",
		"front": "and for this reason",
		"back": "e per questo motivo",
		"whenCreated": "2024-12-17 17:26:10",
		"extras": ""
	}
]